Guide to the Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life records, 1964-2012 UA.09.12.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life records
1964-2012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life
UA.09.12.0002
27.5 Linear Feet
The Duke University Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life serves as a liaison between the university administration and student Greek, fraternity, sorority, and selective living groups. Records contain printed materials; publications; meeting minutes; annual reports; housing reviews; residential hall constitutions and officer lists; Panhellenic alcohol surveys; correspondence; judicial files and letters; and composite photographs related to the administration of Duke University fraternity and sorority programs.
Access Restrictions
Access restricted. For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use of administrative records. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist. Contact Research Services for more information.
Access restricted. In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records. Contact Research Services for more information.
Access note. Collection contains fragile audiovisual/photographic formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
Provenance
The Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a transfer in 2004, 2006, 2012, and 2013.
Collection Overview
Records contain printed materials; publications; meeting minutes; annual reports; housing reviews; residential hall constitutions and officer lists; Panhellenic alcohol surveys; correspondence; judicial files and letters; and composite photographs related to the administration of Duke University fraternity and sorority programs. Administrative documents for Greek Leadership Conferences; Interfraternity Council; and the National Pan-Hellenic Council are also included. In addition to documenting the histories of Panhellenic on-campus groups, the Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life records, 1964-2012 provide material on Duke University students in general, including their social life, political activity, and changing social customs throughout the 20th and 21st centuries.
Biographical / Historical
The Duke University Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life serves as a liaison between university administration, and student fraternity, sorority, and selective living groups. The office advises, serves and supports 38 nationally affiliated chapters and the general Greek community. Following restructuring under Vice President for Student Affairs Larry Moneta in 2002, the Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life was supervised by the Dean of Students. In 2012 the Office was moved to Campus Life under Associate Vice President Zoila Airall. The Fraternity and Sorority was then a free standing Office for four years before moving in 2016 under the University Center for Activities and Events (UCAE), an umbrella center for student clubs and organizations located in Campus Life.
Conditions Governing Access
Access note. Some materials in this collection are fragile audiovisual formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
College students -- Alcohol use -- North Carolina -- Durham; Greek letter societies -- North Carolina -- Durham; Duke University -- Interfraternity Council; African American Greek letter societies; College students -- Housing; Alpha Epsilon Pi; Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity; Alpha Tau Omega; Beta Theta Pi; Delta Kappa Epsilon; Delta Sigma Phi; Kappa Alpha Order; Phi Delta Theta Fraternity; Kappa Sigma Fraternity; Phi Kappa Psi; Pi Kappa Alpha; Psi Upsilon Fraternity; Sigma Alpha Epsilon; Sigma Chi Fraternity; Sigma Nu; Theta Chi; Pi Kappa Phi; Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority; Delta Sigma Theta Sorority; Kappa Alpha Psi Fraternity; Omega Psi Phi Fraternity; Sigma Gamma Rho; Zeta Phi Beta Sorority; Chi Psi; Delta Tau Delta Fraternity; Phi Kappa Sigma Fraternity; Sigma Phi Epsilon; Greek letter societies -- Lambda Pi Chi Sorority; Greek letter societies -- Lambda Phi Epsilon Fraternity; Greek letter societies -- Lambda Upsilon Lambda Fraternity; Greek letter societies -- Theta Nu Xi; Greek letter societies -- Alpha Delta Pi; Delta Gamma; Delta Delta Delta; Kappa Alpha Theta; Kappa Kappa Gamma; Zeta Tau Alpha; Pi Beta Phi; Alpha Phi; Chi Omega Fraternity; Alpha Epsilon Phi; Greek letter societies -- Alpha Omicron Pi; Duke University -- Societies, etc; Duke University -- Students -- Societies, etc; Duke University. Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life
- Accession UA2004-50, 1984-2003
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Alpha Epsilon Pi, Spring 1997 - Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Alpha Phi Alpha, Spring 1999-Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Alpha Tau Omega, Fall 1998–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Beta Theta Pi, Fall 1998–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Delta Kappa Epsilon, Spring 1997–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Delta Sigma Phi, Spring 1994–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Kappa Alpha Order, Spring 1997–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Phi Delta Theta, Fall 1998–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Kappa Sigma, Fall 1992–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Phi Kappa Psi, Fall 1998–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Pi Kappa Alpha, Fall 1999–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Psi Upsilon, Fall 1998–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Sigma Alpha Epsilon, Fall 1992–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Sigma Chi, Fall 1992–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Sigma Nu, Fall 1992–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Fraternity Living Groups: Theta Chi, Fall 1993–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: House BB, Fall 1999 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: Brownstone, Fall 1998–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: Old House CC, Fall 1999–Spring 2000 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: Cleland, Fall 1998–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: Decker (Languages), Fall 1999–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: Maxwell, Fall 1998–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: Mirecourt, Fall 1999–Fall 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: Mitchell (Arts), Fall 1998–Fall 2001 (Box 2)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: Prism, Fall 1998–Fall 2001 (Box 2)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: Round Table, Spring 1999–Fall 2001 (Box 2)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: Scott (Women's Studies), Spring 1997–Fall 2001 (Box 2)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: SHARE, Spring 1999–Fall 2001 (Box 2)
  - Annual Reviews: Selective Living Groups: Wayne Manor, Fall 1993–Fall 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Abele, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Braxton, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Brownstone, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Burton, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Camelot, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Canterbury, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Cleland, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Decker, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Glouchester, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Haight-Ashbury, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Hampton, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Hastings, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: House BB, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: House C, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: House EE, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: House P, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Lancaster, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Maxwell, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Mirecourt, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Nottingham, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Prism, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Roudhouse, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Round Table, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Scott, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: SHARE, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Spectrum, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Stonehenge, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Stratford, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Trent 1, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Trent 2, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Trent 3, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Trent G, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Wannamaker 1, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Wannamaker 3, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Wannamaker 4, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Wellness Residential Hall Proposal (1992) (Box 2)
  - Residential Halls: Residential Halls Old Constitutions/Officer Lists/Miscellaneous: Westminster Windsor York, 2001 (Box 2)
- Accession UA2006-0044, 1982-2012
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Alpha Tau Omega, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Delta Sigma Phi, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Delta Tau Delta, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Kappa Alpha Order, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Kappa Sigma, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Phi Delta Theta, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Phi Kappa Psi, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Pi Kappa Alpha, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Pi Kappa Phi, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Psi Upsilon, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Sigma Chi, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Sigma Nu, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence and Judicial Letters: Interfraternity Council Chapters: Theta Chi, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
- Accession UA2012-0066, 1982-2012
  - House Officers, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Living Groups, 1983-1995 (Box 3)
  - Fraternity Housing, 1977-1994 (Box 3)
  - Fraternity Membership Lists, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Fraternity Membership Lists, Fall, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Fraternity Member Lists, Fall, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Fraternities, 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Fraternities, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Fraternity Lists, Fall, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Fraternity Membership, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Fraternity Membership Lists, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Fraternity Membership Lists, Fall, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Fraternity Statistics Fraternity Lists, Fall, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
  - Fraternity Lists for Fall, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
  - Fraternities, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - Abele, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Braxton, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Brownstone, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Burton, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Camelot, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Canterbury, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Cleland, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Decker, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Glouchester, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Hampton, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Hastings, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - House EE, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - House P, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Lancaster, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Maxwell, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Mirecourt, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Mitchell, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Nottingham, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Round Table, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Road House, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Psi Upsilon, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - SHARE, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - IFC Chapters Documents by Date, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - General IFC documents, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Articles in Non Duke Publications, circa 2012 (Box 4)
  - Newspaper Coverage, 2002-2003 (Box 4)
  - IFC/Greek Press Coverage, 1989-1992 (Box 4)
  - Jessica Cheesborough PA Junior Panhel President, circa 2003 (Box 4)
  - Mu Chapter/Pi Kappa Phi, circa 2004 (Box 4)
  - Historical PR(Chronicle), circa 2005 (Box 4)
  - Panhel Press Clippings, circa 2006 (Box 4)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha Judicial Files, 2002-2003 (Box 4)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha General Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 4)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha Judicial Files, 2001-2004 (Box 4)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha General Correspondence, 1999-2002 (Box 4)
  - Delta Sigma Theta Judicial Files, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi Judicial Files, 2003-2004 (Box 4)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi General Correspondence, 1999-2004 (Box 4)
  - Omega Psi Phi General Correspondence, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Sigma Gamma Rho General Correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 4)
  - Zeta Phi Beta General Correspondence, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi Judicial Files, 2003-2004 (Box 4)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi General Correspondence, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Alpha Tau Omega Judicial Files, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Beta Theta Pi General Correspondence, 1995-2004 (Box 4)
  - Beta Theta Pi Judicial Files, 1992-2004 (Box 4)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon Judicial Files, 1998-1999 (Box 4)
  - Chi Psi General Correspondence, 1995-2004 (Box 4)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon General Correspondence, 1992-2004 (Box 4)
  - Delta Sigma Phi General Correspondence, 2001-2004 (Box 4)
  - Delta Sigma Phi Judicial Files, 2003-2004 (Box 4)
  - Delta Tau Delta General Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 4)
  - Kappa Alpha Order General Correspondence, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Kappa Alpha Order Judicial Files, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Kappa Sigma (Eta Prime) General Correspondence, 1999-2004 (Box 5)
  - Kappa Sigma (Eta Prime) Judicial Files, 2002-2004 (Box 5)
  - Phi Delta Theta Judicial Files, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Phi Delta Theta General Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 5)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma General Correspondence, 1994-2002 (Box 5)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha Judicial Files, 2000-2004 (Box 5)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha General Correspondence, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Pi Kappa Phi General Correspondence, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Phi Kappa Psi Judicial Files, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Phi Kappa Psi General Correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 5)
  - Psi Upsilon General Correspondence, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Sigma Chi General Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 5)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon General Correspondence, 1994-2004 (Box 5)
  - Sigma Nu General Correspondence, 1999-2004 (Box 5)
  - Sigma Nu Judicial Files, 2001-2003 (Box 5)
  - Theta Chi General Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 5)
  - Theta Chi Judicial Files, 2002-2004 (Box 5)
  - Lambda Phi Epsilon General Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 5)
  - Lambda Phi Chi General Correspondence, 1999-2004 (Box 5)
  - Lambda Upsilon Lambda General Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 5)
  - Theta Nu Xi General Correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 5)
  - Alpha Delta Pi Judicial Files, 1992-2004 (Box 5)
  - Alpha Delta Pi General Correspondence, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Delta Gamma General Correspondence, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Delta Delta Delta General Correspondence, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Delta Delta Delta Judicial Files, 1991-2004 (Box 5)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta Judicial Files, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma Judicial Files, 1989-2003 (Box 5)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma General Correspondence, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Zeta Tau Alpha General Correspondence, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Pi Beta Phi Judicial Files, 1992-2004 (Box 5)
  - Panhellenic Sisters of the Semester, circa 2004 (Box 5)
- Accession UA2013-0026, 1964-2011
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access note. Some materials are fragile audiovisual formats that must be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Duke Student Government: DSG Endorsements, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Duke Student Government: Candidate Endorsements, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Duke Student Government: Race Relations/Community Interaction, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Duke Student Government: Candidate Endorsements, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Bryan Center "Re-invention": Proposals, Devil's Desires, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Greek Publicity/Research Info: Greek Life Task Force Report, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Greek Publicity/Research Info: Let Duke Be Duke, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Meetings Backfile: Agendas, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Meetings Backfile: Minutes President: Hilary Holmes, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Meetings Backfile: Agendas, 1999-2000 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Meetings Backfile: Minutes President: Rae Miller, 1999-2000 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Meetings Backfile: Agendas, 2002-2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Meetings Backfile: Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Chapter Presidents Meetings Backfile: Agendas, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Chapter Presidents Meetings Backfile: Agendas, 1999-2000 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Alpha Delta Pi, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Alpha Phi, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Chi Omega, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Delta Delta Delta, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Delta Gamma, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Pi Beta Phi, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Results/Totals, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Alpha Delta Pi, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Alpha Epsilon Phi, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Alpha Omicron Pi, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Alpha Phi, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Chi Omega, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Delta Delta Delta, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Delta Gamma, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Kappa Alpha Theta, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Residential Survey: Pi Beta Phi, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Chapter Presidents Meetings: Agendas, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Southeastern Panhellenic Conference (SEPC): Conference Minutes, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Southeastern Panhellenic Conference (SEPC): National Panhellenic Conference Directory, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Southeastern Panhellenic Conference (SEPC): Meeting, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Southeastern Panhellenic Conference (SEPC): Greek Directory, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Southeastern Panhellenic Conference (SEPC): CEC, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Southeastern Panhellenic Conference (SEPC): Paraphernalia, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Southeastern Panhellenic Conference (SEPC): Guest Speakers, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Panhellenic Council Meeting Minutes/Agendas: Agendas, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Panhellenic Council Meeting Minutes/Agendas: Minutes, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Constitution: NPC Constitution and Unanimous Agreements, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Constitution: Constitutions, Copies, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Constitution: Proposed Amendments, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Rosters: Panhellenic, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Rosters: Panhellenic, 1999-2000 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Rosters: Panhellenic, 2002-2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Officer Transition: Unfoldered, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Officer Transition: Candidate Info Packets, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Officer Transition, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Officer Transition: Surveys, Spring, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Space Concerns: Residential Blocks, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Space Concerns: Residential Life Plans, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Space Concerns: Residential Surveys, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: Newsletter, 1995-1999 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Brochures: Unfoldered, circa 2000 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Brochures: Newsletters, 2002 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Alcohol Policy, Standards: Unfoldered, 2000-2002 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Alcohol Policy, Standards: NPC: Social Activities Alcohol Free Resolution, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: New Member Education: Pledge Education Program, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Total Membership Education: Eating Disorder Programming/Info, 1999-2000 (Box 6)